Guide to the Leon F. Litwack Collection of Berkeley, California, Protest Literature
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Files, Series I; 4; (4 boxes)
  - File 14 (Box 2, Folder 32-34)
    - Committee for a Creative Alternative (org). WHO CARES? On green stock. Docketed: 20 May 68.
    - Committee for a Creative Alternative. AN ALTERNATIVE. Docketed.
    - CORE (org) IT HAPPENED IN BATON ROUGE.
    - CORE (org). JUSTICE?
    - CORE (org). CATALOGUE OF COERCION
    - ELECT LEIGH STEINBERG ASUC SENATE. Docketed.
    - FOR UNLAWFUL CARNAL KNOWLEDGE. Anonymous play dedicated to Allen Ginsberg, 17pp. Cover price is 15 cents. Cover by Peter O. Israel. Gay / Lesbian subject.
    - Free Speech Movement (org) + Peace and Freedom Party (org). BATTLE OF BERKELEY BACKGROUND. Unsigned, undated. Birth of the Peace & Freedom Party, October 2 [1964]. Apparently a contemporary document, concise and accurate, by an activist student.
    - Free Speech Movement (org). BENEFIT CONCERTBrownie McGhee, Sonny Terry et al. LA for Xmas.
    - Free Speech movement documentary history. SAMPLE TELEGRAMS supporting student actions.
    - Free Speech Movement GCC (org). THREE STUDENTS SUSPENDED, ONE DISMISSED, BY STAR-CHAMBER COMMITTEE.
    - Free Speech Movement. THE COURT IN CONTEMPT.
    - GCC (org). ELECTION DELAY.
    - GCC. NOON RALLY GCCTHE REGENTS ARE THROWING THE GRADS OUT OF THE ASUCAGAIN!
    - HEAR YE HEAR YE: JOHN GEORGE. Green stock, docketed. Black politician
    - Highlander Research and Education Center, Inc. (org). HIGHLANDER REPORTS (August 28, 1961-December 31, 1964). Illustrated.
    - Independent Faculty-Student Legal Fund (org). Seeking funds in support of students.
    - INDEPENDENTS.ASUC yellow printed faux check for $257,517.06. May 20, 1968. Docketed.
    - INJUSTICE AT BERKELEY IN THE OBSCENITY CASE.
    - JEREMIAH STAMLER, M.D. LEGAL AID FUND (org). APPEAL FOR FUNDS in open letter to DEAR FRIENDS
    - JEREMIAH STAMLER, M.D. LEGAL AID FUND (org). Contribution sheet, yellow stock.
    - JEREMIAH STAMLER, M.D. LEGAL AID FUND (org). FINANCIAL STATEMENT as of Sept 1, 1966.
    - JOHN R. CROW SPEAKING (various sponsoring orgs).
    - JOIN US IN THE FIGHT FOR HUMAN DIGNITY. Campus student politics, docketed.
    - KENNEDY AIDE AND SPOKESMAN ADAM YARMOLINSKY speaking Tues May 14, [1968]. Docketed.
    - Kent Legal Defense Fund (org). DEAR FRIEND= open letter (illustrated)
    - LET LBJ KNOW WHAT YOU REALLY THINK ABOUT THE WAR IN VIETNAM / March. Red printing on orange stock.
    - Limeliters (org) DEAR FRIENDSnew album announced, first in ten years (some political content)
    - McCARTHY IS HAPPENING. Orange card. Docketed.
    - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Inc. (org). FACT SHEET.
    - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Inc. (org). POVERTY ATTACKS THE HELPLESS.
    - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Inc., West Coast Office (org). CHILDREN AND SCHOOLS
    - New Dialogue I:1 Hayward, CA (Nov 27, 1967). Illus newsprint, docketed.
    - NY Times (org). August 22, 1966 Columns reproduced.
    - OPEN LETTER to Regents, University of California, Berkeley. Unsigned, undated. I urge the regents to reject
    - OPEN LETTER TO THE FACULTY. Docketed.
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org). YOULL BE SORRY Docketed.
    - Postcard to Jeffrey Cohelan, House of Repopen postcard protesting USA govt activity in expanding war in Vietnam
    - REFUSE THE DRAFT-JOIN US. Docketed.
    - REPORT FROM SANTA RITA (Alameda County prison). Docketed, 1967.
    - Resistance (org). DO IT NOW. Docketed.
    - Resistance (org). THE RESISTANCE. On orange paper, 2 leaves. August 31, 1967.
    - Sidney Hillman Foundation (org). THE COURT SITS IN THE CENTER OF THE STORM by Arthuir J. Goldberg. Reprint.
    - Slate (org). THE NEW SLATE. Docketed 14 May 68. Differs from other docketed copy in archive.
    - Slate (org). THE NEW SLATE. Docketed.
    - Socialist Scholars Conference (org). DEAR COLLEAGUE= open letter dated Dec 6, 1965. With form. 3pp in all.
    - Spanish Civil War. COMMEMORATE THE 50th ANNIVERSARY OF THE SPANISH CIVIL WAR. Design by Kerry Tremain.
    - Spanish Civil War. Tom Paine Brigade (org) SPAIN 1936-1986 / A Response to the Abraham Lincoln Brigades version of history. Orange stock.
    - Spanish Civil War. VALB & ALBA (orgs). VETERANS OF THE ABRAHAM LINCOLN BRIGADEWelcomewith envelope.
    - Spanish Civil War. VALB-ALBA in association with Bill Graham (orgs) Ticket to LIVING HISTORY / 50th Anniversary Spanish Civil War, April 27, 1986
    - Spanish Civil War. Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade and the Abraham Lincoln Brigade Archives (orgs). COMMEMORATION program at Berkeley Community Theatre..
    - Stanford Vietnam Day Committee (org). DEAR BAY AREA FACULTY MEMBER= open letter, June 22, 1965.
    - Student Council on Civil Rights (org). SUPPORT FREEDOM IN MISSISSIPPI!
    - Student Union (org). PALMER-TURNER CLAIM ECON PLAN SUCCESS. Docketed.
    - Student Union (org). UNION PARTY ACTION DISCREDITS PROMISES. Docketed.
    - Student Union (org). UNION PARTY ACTION DISCREDITS PROMISES. On yellow stock. Docketed.
    - THE BIG FUNDAMENTAL OMNIPOTENT QUESTION BEFORE THE WORLD TODAY.red, white & blue printing, small slip
    - THE QUARTER SYSTEM: L & S RAILROAD JOB! Noon Rally.
    - THE VIETNAM COMMENCEMENT WILL BE HELD TODAYUC faculty sign on (in part) & participate. May 17, 1968. Docketed.
    - TIME TO RELAX (on yellow stock) with McCARTHY IS HAPPENING / Cow Palace May 22. Docketed. The latter piece, stapled on, is a duplicate.
    - U.A. Undergraduate Association (org). FACULTY / STUDENT DEBATE. Suzanne Goldberg & Mario Savio vs Searle & Malia
    - UC Berkeley Students for Kennedy. FINAL EXAMS ARE AN ESTABLISHMENT TRICK. Docketed.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). DRAFT STATEMENT ON DUE PROCESS IN CASES WHERE A SEVERE PENALTY SUCH AS EXPULSION, DISMISSAL, OR SUSPENSION IS CONTEMPLATED. December 8, 1964.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). STATEMENT OF POLICY, Oct 2, 1968. Docketed.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate. (org). Minutes, Berkeley Division, December 4, 1967. 10pp.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Office of the Chancellor. STATEMENT BY CHANCELLOR Roger W. Heyns. May 20, 1969.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Office of the Chancellor. TO THE CAMPUS COMMUNITY from Vice Chancellor of Student Affairs, William B. Boyd. Nov 13, 1967.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Spider Magazine. (org). SHAME.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Undergraduate Association (org). ATTENTION ATTENTION ATTENTION.
    - Universities Committee on the Problems of War and Peace of Greater New York. DEAR COLLEAGUE= open letter, 2 + pp.
    - University Art Museum (org). JEAN-LUC GODARD Retrospective. Peach paper, illustrated, docketed.
    - University Bulletin 16:17 (Dec 11, 1967)
    - Vietnam Day Committee. PROTEST HYPOCRISY / PICKET JOHNSON.
    - Wall Street Journal clipping
    - War Tax Resistance (org). A CALL TO WAR TAX RESISTANCE.
    - War Tax Resistance. DEAR FRIEND=open letter from Bradford Lyttle, March 16, 1970.
  - File 15 (Box 2, Folder 35-37)
    - ad hoc Committee of Concerned Students (org). WHERE IS REASON?...THINK. Variant, this copy on yellow stock and docketed.
    - ad hoc Committee of Concerned Students (org). WHERE IS REASON?...THINK. Variant, this copy on yellow stock and docketed variant
    - ad hoc Committee on Protest for Polish Political Freedom (org). PROTEST IMPRISONMENT OF POLISH SOCIALISTS.
    - Ad Hoc Faculty Observers Committee (org). TO THE MEMBERS OF THE ACADEMIC SENATE. March 4, 1969. 5pp.
    - AN INVITATIONsigned by professors etc. Docketed, 1968.
    - ASUC (org) PLEASE VOTE FOR RAY F. BIETZ (pink stock). Docketed.Union party, ASUC. (org). SANDY KRESSOrange stock. Docketed.
    - ASUC (org). DEAR FACULTY MEMBER= open letter signed in type by Steve Gompertz
    - ASUC Senate (student org). DEAR FACULTY MEMBER= open letter signed in type by John McKenzie.
    - Bay Area Spartacist League (org). SPARTACIST PRINTER SUBPOENAED IN LATEST ATTACK ON ANTI-WAR MOVEMENT. Orange stock. Docketed.
    - Berkeley Chapter Young Americans for Freedom (org). THE 11 NON-NEGOTIABLE DEMANDS OF THE RIGHT WORLD LIBERATIO FRONT. Buff stock. Docketed.
    - Berkeley Defense Committee. THERES A CONSPIRACY AFLOATillus Benefit Dance for the Berkeley Three
    - Berkeley Faculty Branch, AFT (org). STATEMENT OF PURPOSE, 2pp
    - Berkeley Faculty Union, Executive Committee (org). THE COMMON SENSE OF FACULTY POWER. 11 leaves
    - BERKELEY PEACE VIGIL. Sunday April 9. Illustrated by Arno Fleischer.
    - Berkeley Vietnam Day Committee (org). STREET DANCE AND RALLY. Friday, August 5.
    - Berkeley W.E.B. Dubois Club (org). SUBPOENA TO AN OPEN INVESTIGATION
    - Black Panther Party (org) WHO IS HUEY NEWTON? Docketed, 1968.
    - Black Panther Party / Campus Friends of STDW (orgs). MASS MEEDING WED / Members of Oakland Seven will speak. Docketed.
    - Buxbaum (Richard M.) faculty of LAW, University of California, Berkeley. TO MEMBERS OF THE FACULTY AT BERKELEY. Open letter, March 3, 1969. 2pp. Docketed.
    - Cal Conservatives for Political Action (org). ESCALATE THE MIND NOT THE WAR
    - Campus Friends of AFT 1570 (org). PEOPLE OR QUAIL?
    - Campus Friends of AFT, No. 1570. RALLY TODAY / WEDNESDAY NOOK / SPROUL PLAZA.
    - Campus Independent Socialist Club (org). DECLARATION OF WAR.
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org)
    - Campus Mobilization Committee (org). PLAN & BUILD THE INTNL STUDENT STRIKE, illustrated. Docketed.
    - Campus Report 3:10 (March 6, 1969)
    - Campus SDS.DOW-ONE OF MANY. Green stock. Docketed.
    - Campus Stop the Draft Week (org) ITS HIT THE FAN, BABY. Docketed.
    - Campus YSA (org) UNION MILITANTS LOOK AT AFT. Docketed.
    - Campus YSL (org). CHICANOillustrated. Pink stock. Docketed.
    - CELEBRATE INTERNATIONAL WOMENS DAY. Docketed.
    - Christian World Liberation Front. HEY GOD, I GOT BUSTED!
    - Citizens Against Legalized Murder (CALM) (org). HELP END LEGALIOZED MURDER IN CALIFORNIA. Green stock.
    - Committee for Participant Education. INITIATE YOUR OWN COURSE Docketed
    - Concerned Berkeley Parents (org). CONCERNED BERKELEY PARENTS AND FRIENDS STATEMENT OF BELIEFS AND OBJECTIVES. Orange stock.
    - Copley (Robert H.) THE PEACE PLAN (illustrated)
    - CORE (org) JOIN CORE IN THE FIGHT AGAINST BIGOTRY IN THE OAKLAND SCHOOLS.
    - DEAR COLLEAGUE= open letter from 11 University of California, Berkeley professors
    - DEAR COLLEAGUE= open letter in re indictment of Dr. Spock. Jan 27, 1968. Three leaves, envelope. Docketed
    - DEAR FACULTY MEMBER= open letter signed in type by six faculty members
    - DEAR= open letter, cover.unsignedcalling for telegrams to be sent to chair of Board of Regents, Edward W. Carter
    - Emergency Committee for Vietnamese Relief. (org). QUESTIONS AND ANSWERS.3pp.
    - Emergency Committee for Vietnamese Relief. (org). WE ARE AMERICAN CITIZENS.. Blue stock.
    - English Graduate Association, Steering Committee (org). DEAR EDITOR= open letter, 23 May 1969
    - Faculty Memers & Forum International (org). University of California, Berkeley CONFERENCE ON NIGERIA-BIAFRA RELIEF DAYS OF THE HYENAS (play) Docketed, 1969.
    - FIFTEEN YEARS IN PRISON FOR THIS! Illustrated. Docketed.
    - FREE SPEECH FOR ANDREI SINYAVSKY AND YURI DANIEL Monday 21
    - Free Speech Movement (org). PROVISIONAL PLATFORM
    - Freuhan (George J.) senior, UCB. SOLUTION OR DIVERSION? Third copy, but variant docket: handout on campus Mon AM 5 Dec
    - FSL (org) Free Speech MovementON KERRS MANIPULATIONS. Yellow stock.
    - GENERAL STUDENT STRIKE
    - GI Civilian Easter Peace March (org). APRIL 6 GI-CIVILIAN PEACE MARCH (illustrated)
    - Graduate Coordinating Council (org). LEGAL INFO SHEET
    - Heyns (Roger W.) Chancellor, University of California, Berkeley. A STATEMENT. Docketed: 5 Dec, Monday, handout on campus.
    - Heyns (Roger W.) Chancellor, University of California, Berkeley. A STATEMENT. Variant docket.
    - Instant News Service 1:11 (Wed May 11, 1969). Illustrated newsprint.
    - Institute for Historical Review (org). OPEN LETTER, 1 October 1980. With envelope, order form for books; four-page brochure & Legion for the Survival of Freedom illustrated envelope.
    - MAPS (org). MAPS REPORTS. Docketed.
    - Marr (David) et all. WHY A NEW ASIAN STUDIES DEPT?? / An Overdue Challenge to Scholarship on Asia. Peach stock cover, 3 leaves, 1969. Docketed
    - Middlekauf (Robert) + Scheiner (Irwin) University of California, Berkeley History professors. A NOTE ON THE ACADEMIC SENATES POWERS AND STUDENT DISCIPLINE.
    - MOTHER AND CHILD
    - NOW LISTEN CHILDREN IM GOING TO TELL YOU= first line, illustrated broadside poem, anonymous. Docketed, 1968.
    - PEACE ROCK concert at Fillmore Aud Sat Feb 12
    - Peoples Park. PEOPLES PARK IS AS OF MAY 15, 1969. Map.
    - Peoples Park. PUBLIC MEETING / LETS OPEN THE PARK TO THE PEOPLE! (various orgs sponsored).
    - Police Committee / Soc. 118 (org). THE POLICE (CHP) & U. C. Berkeley. 4pp. Docketed, 1969.
    - PROGRAM / CONGRESS OF UNREPRESENTED PEOPLES
    - Radical Students Union (RSU). BENEFIT DANCE. Docketed.
    - Reichek (Jesse) architecture, University of California, Berkeley. TO ALL MEMBERS OF THE UNIVERSITY COMMUNITY.
    - Scriven (Michael) PROS AND CONS OF FACULTY UNIONS. United Federation of Teachers Berkeley Campus letterhead, 5pp.
    - Sealey (Raphael) TO FACULTY AND TEACHING ASSISTANTS, Dept of History. Jan 30, 1968. Docketed.
    - SHOWDOWN
    - Sir George Williams University, Montreal. DEAR SIR= open letters from members of the .academic community as individuals, March 21, 1969 + 12pp document, an essay defending the school against charges of racism
    - Smith (Henry Nash) professor of English, University of California, Berkeley. WHY HAS THE FACULTY FAILED TO CONDEMN VIOLATIONS OF THE LAW BY STUDENTS.
    - Spanish Civil War. IN MADRID AND MISSISSIPPI. Bay Area Post of the Veterans of the Abraham Lincoln Brigade. Feb 25, 2001
    - STRIKE NOW..FLUNK LATER (variant?)
    - STRIKE NOWFLUNK LATER. Docketed copy. Another copy elsewhere in archive.
    - Student Mobilization Committee (org) INTERNATIONAL STUDENT-FACULTY STRIKE APRIL 26th.
    - Taxpayers Against War (org). TAXPAYERS AGAINST WAR. 4 leaves, stapled.
    - THE BERKELEY ACADEMIC PLAN REVEALED [hostile]. (16) pp.
    - Third World Faculty and Administrators Alliance (TWFAA) (org). Open letter, March 4, 1969.
    - Third World Liberation Front = TWLF (org). THIRD WORLD COLLEGE DAY. Docketed.
    - TO ALL STUDENTS AND FACULTY= open letter from 17 professors
    - TO THE CAMPUS COMMUNITY, June 3, 1969. Five professors protest dismissal proceedings against President-elect of the ASUC, Mr. Daniel Siegel.
    - TUESDAY BAND JAM. Grateful Dead on April 9-12, etc.
    - TWLF (org). THIRD WORLD COLLEGE DAY.
    - TWLF WHERE WE STAND / THE STRIKE GOES ON. Docketed, 1969.
    - University of California, Berkeley a group of faculty members. STATEMENT TO THE CITIZENS OF CALIFORNIA.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Academic Senate (org). REPORT OF THE COMMITTEE ON SENATE POLICY / STATE OF THE CAMPUS MESSAGE. May 6, 1969. 26pp.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Chancellor Roger W. Heyns. CHARTER DAY REMARKS. April 24, 1969, 6pp.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Office of the Chancellor. STATEMENT OF CHANCELLOR ROGER W. HEYNS. May 13, 1969. 4pp.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Office of the Chancellor. TO THE CAMPUS COMMUNITY. .-= open letter dated April 23, 1969, from Vice Chancellor L. L. Sammet.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Report of the President VALUES AND VISIONS1958-1964. 56pp.
    - University Bulletin 17:38 (June 2, 1969).
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org) RESERVISTS AND MEN OF DRAFT AGE.
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). PRESENTS WORLD PREMIEREdocumentary film
    - Vietnam Day Committee (org). STOP THE TROOP TRAIN.
    - Vietnam Day Committee SILENT DEMONSTRATION illustrated / verso: DEMONSTRATE WITH:
    - VIETNAM: AN APPEAL TO THE FACULTY. By 14 professors (duplicate?)
    - Voters Pledge Campaign. Mailer.
  - File 16 (Box 2, Folder 38-40)
    - A POLICEMAN WANTS TO KNOW, 4pp. Purple stock / pink stock
    - ABOUT THE SPEAKERS (at Wheeler Hall, University of California, Berkeley): Linus Pauling, Buckminster Fuller et al
    - Ad Hoc Committee Against a Vietnam War in the Middle East (CAVME) FIRST NATIONAL MIDDLE EAST TEACH-IN
    - ANSWER NIXON IN THE STREETS! Orange stock.
    - ARFEP (Berkeley Chapter) CHINA EXISTS!
    - Associated Students of San Francisco State College (org). To: ALL STUDENTS= open letter, 5pp
    - ASUC Resource Center for Democratic Education (org) FREE SPEECH MOVEMENT / 20th Anniversary Project
    - Berkeley Faculty Union AFT 1474 (org). REPORT FROM3pp.
    - Black Panther Party (org) + People in Defense of Eldridge Cleaver (org). SUPPORT VIGIL FOR ELDRIDGE CLEAVER
    - Black Panther Party (org) in part / SDS (org). Films: ON STRIKE & OIL STRIKE & MAY DAY (Black Panther film). Yellow stock.
    - Black Panther Party (org). BLACK PANTHER PEACE AND FREEDOM / NEWTON-SEALE / CongressSTATE ASSEMBLY. Bumper sticker in orange and blue.
    - Black Panther Party (org). HUEY NEWTON FOR U.S. Congress / Bobby Seale for State Assembly. 4pp.
    - Blackmens Draft Alliance (org). BROTHERS AND SISTERSHELL NO!! WE WONT GO!!. Blue stock.
    - Cal Conservatives for Political Action (org). IN DEFENSE OF THE OAKLAND TRIBUNE.
    - Callison (Bill) + Ker (Susan) AN OPPORTUNITY
    - Campus Students for a Democratic Society (org). FIGHT RACISM JOIN THE STRIKE. Yellow stock.
    - Campus Young Socialist Alliance (org). BLACK NATIONALISM AND SOCIALISM. Blue ink.
    - Center for Participant Education (org) DEAR FRIEND= open letter. Blue stock.
    - CIVIL DISOBEDIENCE AND THE AMERICAN DEMOCRATIC TRADITION: A THOUGHTFUL EXAMINATION OF THE USE AND MISUSE OF CIVIL DIAOBEDIENCE IN A DEMOCRACY. RESPONSE SHEET.
    - CIVIL DISOBEDIENCE AND THE DEMOCRATIC TRADITION
    - Committee for a Progressive Middle East (org) DEAR PROFESSOR= open letter, purple ink, page 1 only
    - Committee for Non-Violent Action & War Resisters League (orgs). TO END THE WAR IN VIETNAM rally (illustrated)
    - CONCERNED STUDENTS OF THE UNIVERSITY ARE OPPOSED TO VIOLENCE[= first line] Blue stock.
    - CORE (Berkeley) LETS FINISH THE JOB !! Yellow stock
    - CPE Course descriptions. Blue stock
    - DAMN DDT DAY. Malvina Reynolds appeared. Art by Lobdell.
    - Dellums (Ron) Congressman 8th District. On UC Nuclear Weapons Labs Conversion Project. DEAR FRIENDS= open letter
    - DRAFT TEXT OF WEST COAST NYTIMES FULL PAGE ADVERTISEMENT, TO BE SIGNED BY FACULTY SYSTEMWIDE AT UC. 2 leaves.
    - East Bay Labor Journal AFL/CIO (org). Ad hoc Committee GETS UNANIMOUS ENDORSEMENT, reprinted from the Sept 18, 1964 edition. / verso: PUT AN END TO DISCRIMINATION AT THE OAKLAND TRIBUNE.
    - EITHER EUPHORIC OR AGAINST US. Poem = installment #2. Free poetry by Octopus. Purple ink.
    - Fillmore West card JOE COCKERLITTLE RICHARDGRATEFUL DEAD [at Winterland November 24-25 etc. Illustrated.
    - Findley (Tim) I WAS A PRISONER AT SANTA RITA. (from SF Chronicle). Illustrated verso with other text.
    - FOR MAYOR OF BERKELEY JERRY RUBIN (26pp). Cover torn. Art work by Tom Weller.
    - Free Speech Movement (org) A SPECTRE IS HAUNTING THE UNIVERSITY OF CALIFORNIA
    - Free Speech Movement. STRIKE FOR FREEDOM
    - Free Speech Movement. STRIKE FOR FREEDOM (variant)
    - Free Speech Movement Reunion (org). DEAR FRIENDS= open letter
    - GCC (org). DECEMBER 8.
    - IF HOWARD COSELL CAN TEACH AT YALE, WHY CANT HERBERT APTHEKER? 4pp.
    - Jeremiah Stamler, M.D. Legal Aid Fund (org.) Pledge sheet.
    - Kay, Phillips & Gumperz STATEMENT TO THE CITIZENS OF CALIFORNIA
    - LETS WIN IN VIETNAM. Bumper sticker in black and cerise.
    - Liberation Press (org). RESIST THE DRAFT NOV. 14. Illustrated.
    - Militant Labor Forum (org). HEAR: ERNEST MANDEL, Illustrated. Blue ink.
    - NAACP Legal Defense and Educational Fund, Inc. (org). ALABAMATHE TEST OF FREEDOM
    - New University Conference (org). THE RADICAL TEACHER. 32pp.
    - Nov 14 Committee; SMC; Vets for Peace; RSU; YSA; IS (and other orgs). HELP BUILD NOV 14 STRIKE. Illustrated.
    - Peace and Freedom Movement (org). FOR Supervisor Jones. Bumper sticker in blue and yellow. Black candidate. END WAR AND RACISM.
    - Peace and Freedom Party (org). SOKOL / ELECT THE HEAD, YELLEADER. Illustrated.
    - Peoples Park + RSU (org) BULLETIN / POLICE POLLUTE PARK
    - Peoples Park + RSU (org). WE WILL NOT INITIATE ANY VIOLENCE BUT Illustrated. Purple ink.
    - Peoples Park SOD BROTHER (illustrated) / SAVE PEOPLES PARK.
    - Peoples Park. WHO OWNS THE PARK? Illustrated. Yellow stock.
    - PL / Berkeley PL News / A Communist Viewpoint (org). FIGHT RULERS TERROR / BUILD A REVOLUTIONARY MOVEMENT.. 8pp, illus.
    - PRINCIPLES OF HUMANITY / verso: UNIVERSAL VOICE. yellow stock.
    - Progressive Labor Party (org). ON TRIAL FOR FIGHTING RACSIM.
    - Project National Interest (org). OPEN LETTER, personalized to Professor Leon Litwack, 2 leaves. Light tan stock.
    - Radical Action Union (org) PRESENTS CHARLES GARRY speaking on the Chicago Conspiracy Trial (illustrated). Light pink stock.
    - Radical Action Union PRESENTS STRIKE FORUM. Orange stock, illustrated
    - Radical History Review 3:4 (Fall 1976).
    - Radical Student Union (org) MEETING Wednesday
    - Resistance (Oakland). (org). DRAFT TRIALS.
    - RSU (org). Film: Alain Resnais LA GUERRE EST FINIE. Blue stock.
    - San Francisco Legal Defense Committee (org). INSANITY IN THE COURTS. Illustrated., 12pp booklet.
    - Savio (Mario) page two of a two-page doc, signed in blue ink (in facsimile). 20th anniversary commemoration of Free Speech Movement
    - Savio (Mario) et al STATEMENT ON THE MIDDLE EAST, 4pp.
    - SDS (org). ADMINISTRATION ATTACKS SDS & GATER-2 ARRESTED.
    - SDS. WHAT IS ALL THIS TALK ABOUT WOMENS LIBERATION?
    - SF State Student Mobilization Committee. HELP BUILD THE VIETNAM MORATORIUM. Illustrated.
    - SIGN A TELEGRAM TO SENATOR RICHARD B. RUSSELL
    - Slate & WEB DuBois Club (orgs). THE AD-HOC COMMITTEE TO END DISCRIMINATIONOAKLAND TRIBUNE
    - SMC (org). BUILD VIETNAM WEEK. Pink stock.
    - SMC (org). MEETING THURS 23 Oct. Illus. Yellow stock.
    - Socialist Labor Party (org). WAR WHY? (newsprint, 4pp)
    - Spartacist Committee (org) THE HARLEM RIOTS Yellow stock
    - SSC (org). THIRD WORLD COLLEGE DAY.
    - Statewide Strike Support Organizing Committee. MASS CONVERGENCE ON S.F. STATE January 6-13. / verso: partial list of endorsers.
    - Student Mobilization Committee. GI RALLY. Illustrated.
    - Student Mobilizing Committee (org). HELP BUILD A MASSIVE DEMONSTRATIONMeeting (illustrated)
    - Students for a Democratic Society (org). THE UNIVERSITY IS A BOSS
    - Superb (org). PRESENTSSIDE SHOW / MINSTREL SHOWLeslie Perrry on Frederick Douglass. Illustrated. Yellow stock. Announcement.
    - SUPPORT OUR TROOPS / NO IRAQ WAR!
    - SURVIVAL DAY (illustrated)
    - SURVIVAL DAY October 25 (illustrated) with attached: AND NO ONE NEED LOOK AT/ HARSH REALITY (illus)
    - Telegraph Avenue Liberation Front (org). Peoples Park. TALF FREE FOOD
    - THE FIGHT AGAINST RACISM. Illustrated.
    - University of California, Berkeley Faculty Peace Committee (org). TEACH-OUT AGAINST THE WAR WEDNESDAY, January 30 all day. Orange text.
    - University of California, Berkeley Faculty Peace Committee (org).. INVITATION TO JOIN.
    - University of California, Berkeley. Student-Faculty Ad Hoc Peace Committee (org). PRESENTS RE-AFFIRMATION DAY.
    - Veterans for Peace (org). WE ARE VETERANS OF THE UNITED STATED ARMED FORCES= first line. Blue stock.